The
year was 1985, and the number one show on
TV was Evil Brat!
The show starred young Balthazar Brat as a
child prodigy.
Brat was the biggest
child actor of the 1980s,
striking a chord with
audiences all over the world.
But it all came to an end in Season
3, when... I've been a bad boy!
The young star experienced an unexpected
growth spurt.
The show was cancelled.
Hollywood rejected him, and Brat quickly
plunged into a downward spiral,
starting to actually believe he was the
character he played on TV.
What are you looking at?
Leading us all to wonder...
Where is he now?
You know what, Clive?
Playing a villain on TV was fun,
but being one in real life is even better!
Heist music!
Here he comes!
Ow!
What?
Clive, what are you music?
Sorry, my bad.
I'm scared of you.
I'm going to get you!
Sir, the ship has been boarded by some
kind of monster!
Wait, that's not a monster!
That's a man wearing shoulder pads!
There's only one supervillain whose
fashion sense is quite that dated.
Balthazar Brat!
Blast it, the Jumont Diamond is on that
ship!
I want every agent in the area on the
scene immediately!
We're here!
Agents Grucy are closing fast!
Yes!
Wait, why?
What did you call us?
Grucy!
You know, Gru and Lucy mushed together.
Try it!
I like it, but not a lot.
I don't like it.
Huh?
Gru?
We can make it!
No, we can't!
Who's bad?
Get ready for-
Hey, how you doing?
Are you okay?
You guys are so cute.
Go get him, Gru-Gru!
Hello, Gru.
How's your transition coming?
You know, from world's worst villain to
world's worst agent?
Oh, that's hilarious.
You should be on TV.
Oh, that's right!
You were!
But then you got cancelled!
What about that?
What?
Oh, corals!
Dance fight!
Die to be dead!
Alpha Team, the diamond is secure.
Come and pick up the package.
Copy that.
Alpha Team, in approach.
Gru!
Did you actually think I was unconscious?
It's called acting, Hoser.
And clearly I've still got it!
I've been a bad boy!
Son of a... Betamax!
Go, go!
Get him!
He's getting away!
This isn't over, Gru.
You hear me?
This is not over!
Yeah?
Well, I still have the diamond!
Happy birthday, dear Dan!
Happy birthday to you!
I
can't believe Brad got away again!
How is this possible?
How?
And it's not just that he got away,
it's that he's so smug about it!
I've been a bad boy!
Edna!
Hey!
Looking hot!
Today.
Got the cats on you.
And it was so humiliating, dangling there
in the bubblegum speedo!
And I didn't have time to go to the gym
this week, and I had a big breakfast!
I was feeling a little bloated!
You know what?
He's not even worth talking about.
I don't even want to waste another breath
about the guy!
And another thing!
Next time I see Brad, I will moonwalk all
over his stupid face!
Oh, despicable me.
Thank you all for coming at such short
notice.
It is with great sadness
that I inform you that
as of today, I am retiring
as head of the AVL.
Oh, no!
Your new leader is coming directly from
head office.
Effective immediately.
She is the very gifted, very ambitious
Miss Valerie DaVinci.
As I look out over all your faces,
I am flooded with so many memories.
Oh, boy!
This is a snooze fest!
Blah, blah, blah!
We understand!
You're old, you're fat, you're dumb!
Let me breathe in!
Oh, broke a little sweat there.
First order of business.
Which one of you losers is Agent Groove?
Oh, that would be me.
Although, I don't know if I'd say loser,
per se.
Kind of is...
Oh, it's the girls!
Not a good time!
Hey!
Yes, sir!
Ma'am, you're making me nervous.
How could you let Balthazar Bratt, the
AVL's most wanted villain, just get away?
That is the opposite of what we do here!
Okay, okay, yes.
Maybe he got away again.
But he didn't get the diamond,
and I am this close to bringing him in.
This close!
Ha!
Interesting.
You're fired!
What?
That's totally not fair!
Gru is a great agent!
This subtitle has been error.
Well, yes she did.
Honey, you didn't have to do that.
I know how much you love your job.
Well, I love other things more.
You know, we're going to have to tell the
girls.
Can you do it?
The whole mom thing is still kind of new
to me.
Oh, sure.
Hello?
This is unexpected.
Well, you never got to go on a honeymoon,
so-We made you dinner!
It's a luau!
We got pineapples and coke and that's the
nuca lady!
Oh, yay!
The soup of the day, madame.
And monsieur?
The gummy bears were my idea.
Mmm, looks so good to even eat!
Am I right?
But I made it for you.
Good soup!
I love the combination of gummy bears with
meat!
I'm going to hold it in my mouth, because
it's so good I don't want to swallow it.
So, how was work?
Oh, did you take that guy down?
Did anything explode?
Well, actually, today Lucy and I were
invited to not work at the ABL anymore.
No!
You got fired?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes.
But don't worry.
I'm sure we'll get new jobs real soon.
Even better ones.
What's better than being super cool secret
agents?
Oh, I know.
You can gamble online.
That's what Katie's dad does.
Okay, we will definitely look into that.
That's a good suggestion.
And let's not go over to Katie's house
anymore.
Hmm?
Guys, I don't think you've heard me right.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
This does not mean that we are going back
to being villains.
Pinyu, flacomico!
Okay, all right.
I get it.
Look, I know it's been a little tough
lately.
Especially with Dr. Nefario accidentally
freezing himself in carbonite.
But our life of crime is over.
Now, now, you're with me on this,
right?
Guys, listen to me.
Read my lips.
Listen me lipo.
Pomodoro wacomquit.
What did I say?
It's not comquit?
Oh, okay.
Pomodoro wacomquit.
Don't take the tongue with me.
We're not going back to villainy.
Yes, and I don't want to hear another word
about it.
Look, if you guys don't stop right now,
there will be consequences.
Hey, don't say anything you're going to
regret.
You're serious?
Come on.
No, no, no, no, no.
Pudgy?
Hey, Jerry!
Great news, guys.
You have been promoted.
You're in charge now.
Not bad.
Yee-bah!
Rooba, Rooba, Rooba, Rooba, Rooba,
Rooba!
Jish!
Ah, Monsieur Pompe,
to what do we owe the
presence of the world's
foremost gem expert?
The chief of police sent me.
He was concerned that
during the recent heist
attempt, the Dumont diamond
was replaced with a phony.
Huh?
Now, you have been duped.
What?
We have?
Yes.
By me!
But what is...
Oh, should I say.
..
Je suis ce mauvais gosseau!
No!
Hey, girl.
What you doing down here?
In the dark?
Alone?
Oh, nothing.
Just thinking.
You okay?
Oh, yes.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
It's just... Ah, I don't know.
I guess I just feel like a failure.
Like I don't have a purpose anymore.
Hey, Mister, you are not a failure.
If only I could have nailed Brad.
So many times I almost had him.
But now I'll never get the chance,
because I have been kicked to the curb.
Gru, you've got to let this go.
It's time to look forward.
Things will get better, I promise.
Excuse me.
Pardon me, young people.
Would you tell me how to get to this
address?
I'm looking for a Mr. Gru.
Idiots.
No!
Kyle!
Stop!
Kyle, let go!
No, no!
You've got to be kidding me!
Lucy, did you see... He helps
you if you have nightmare.
And he's really good to snuggle with.
Oh, no, no, no.
Agnes, Agnes!
No.
Take good care of him.
Thank you!
Agnes, what are you doing?
You sold your unicorn?
I just wanted to help, since you don't
have a job.
I got two whole dollars for it.
Excuse me.
Sorry, buddy, the sale's over.
Yes, but this will
only take a... Hey!
Eyebrows!
Get off the lawn!
Yeah, but... Hey, could
you... Oh, of course.
Now, as I was saying...
Oh, goodbye!
Listen, Agnes, you don't need to worry.
We're going to be fine.
For real?
For real.
Now, come on, let's pack this stuff up.
Seriously?
Buddy, you're not getting the...
Excuse me, Mr. Groove, but I really must
have a word with you.
How do you know my name?
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Groove.
Ow!
Good puppy!
And I am inquiring on behalf of your twin
brother, Groove.
He needs your help.
What?
Twin brother?
Big brother?
Oh, yeah.
He would like to fly you to Fredonia to
meet him.
Your father has recently passed
away, and... Oh, okay, Coco.
I'm sorry, but my dad died when I was a
baby.
And I don't have any brother.
You got the wrong guy.
Really?
Well, then, how do you explain this?
You what?
Ha ha ha!
Bellissimo!
Oh, hello, Groove.
Hi, Mom.
It's important to keep active in one's
golden years.
There you are, you cutie!
These are my diving instructors,
Vincenzo and Paolo.
Ciao, boys.
So, what do you want?
Mom, do I have a twin brother?
How did you find out?
Who told you?
Wait, what?
It's true!
You never told me I had a brother!
And you told me that dad died of
disappointment when I was born!
Yeah, yeah.
That was the agreement.
Agreement?
What are you talking about?
Shortly after you and your brother were
born, your father and I divorced.
We each took one son to raise on our own
and promised never to see each other again.
Obviously, I got second pick.
I have a brother.
Hey, girls!
How are things in row B, huh?
I put together some fun activities for the
trip.
Who is up for some gin rummy?
Yeah, um, we're good.
Oh, okay.
I'll just sit here and play solitaire.
I hope I win.
I wonder what the row will be like.
Maybe we'll have the twin thing when you
can read each other's minds.
No?
How cool would that be?
Um, super cool.
I can't wait to meet my brother!
What's with all the pigs?
This is the family business.
The largest pig farm in the whole of
Fredonia.
Okay, nice pig.
Now, that's my private part.
This pig has issues!
Please, come in.
Blah!
Oh,
this is amazing!
It's like the Sistine Chapel!
But with pigs...
My brother!
Brother, I am so happy!
After all of these years, finally I'm
meeting you!
Yup, alright, cut!
Oh, look at that!
You must be the beautiful wife!
Beautiful?
Oh, that's a dog!
Sweet talker.
How is my brother finding a wife like you
when he is so bald?
I'm joking!
This must be my nieces!
You're Agnes!
You are small with big eyes!
And it makes me want to put you in my
pocket!
You can't do that!
I'm too big!
He did!
I can tell that you are a little
mischievous!
We're going to have to make a little
trouble later.
What?
I already have!
Ow!
Please!
This must be mischievous behavior!
And Margo, oh, you are so mature,
I'm guessing.
Why, are you fifteen?
Fifteen?
She's twelve.
She looks twelve and will always be
twelve.
So, Drew, this place is amazing!
I mean, you just walk through the doors
and you're like...
It's nice, I guess, sure.
I'm not really into things.
Yes, the best!
Alright, let's go home now.
Home?
Why?
I don't know.
This guy with the mansion
and the cars and all
the hair with the silky
smooth luxurious hair.
I feel worse than I did before I came.
He's your brother, Drew.
Give this a chance.
Oh, I was thinking while
Drew and I catch up on some
brother stuff, you girls
should go with friends.
He has a surprise for you.
Yay!
Awesome!
I love surprises!
Oh, this is perfect!
Mother-daughter bonding time.
Let's do it!
Bye!
You boys have fun!
Whoopee!
Now you can be as evil as
Balthazar Brat with the Evil Brat
action figure featuring
music-activated break-dance mode.
Also featuring bubblegum-launching
shoulder pads.
And the all-new Mega Diamond Laser!
No more masks!
I've been a bad boy!
Mega Diamond Laser does not actually
incinerate books.
How could Hollywood cancel a show that
produced toys like this, Clive?
Evil Brat was a masterpiece!
Does no one value true art anymore?
It's a disgrace and a travesty,
sir.
Well, now that I've got the diamond,
it's payback time.
Oh, it's too bad Gru won't be around to
try and stop me.
Oh, wait!
No, it's not!
I hate that dweeb!
And you, Hollywood!
This time, I'm canceling you and all the
losers who rejected me!
So, how are things going for you
career-wise?
Great!
So, so great!
Crushing it!
Well, I've got something that I think
you'll find very interesting.
Hold on to your face, brother!
What is all this?
The pig farm was just a cover for the real
family business.
Oh!
Hey, it's Gru with boobs!
Now, feast your eyes on...
Dad's Lair!
Ta-da!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait, so our dad was a villain?
No, no, no!
Not just a villain, but one of the
greatest of all time!
He was known as the Bald Terror!
That's him?
Our dad?
He was so proud of you and what a great
villain you were!
He was?
For me?
Not so much.
To dad, I was just a failure.
Never thought I had what it took to be a
villain.
But now you can help me prove him wrong!
Brother, teach me the art of villainy!
No, no, no, no.
I can't do that.
What?
But it's our family tradition!
You can't say no to that!
Look, I'm sorry.
I left that life behind me.
End of story.
Oh... Okay, I understand.
I wonder what this does.
No, no, no, no!
Holy moly!
Dad's villain wheels!
Pretty slick!
Hey, you wanna take her out for a spin?
Just for some fun?
Zero to 403 seconds!
Able to withstand a nuclear blast!
I'm to the D!
Oh, yeah, that's pretty nice!
And it's a hybrid!
Look out!
Help me!
I am not enjoying this!
Wow,
what is going on here?
Welcome to the annual Fredonian Cheese
Festival!
Go!
Lucy, can we get these, please?
Okay, but only one each.
I mean it.
Aw, man!
No, I don't.
Get as many as you want.
I don't care.
Yay!
Awesome!
Uh... What?
Well, it's okay to tell them no.
Sometimes, too.
You know?
Moms need to be tough.
Right, right.
Tough.
Good one.
I can totally do that.
You know, still figuring out this mom
thing.
Getting my silly legs.
Maybe.
It's a unicorn!
Um, sure, yeah.
But first, let's,
um... Oh, look!
It's a traditional Fredonian dance.
How amazing does that look?
Say Say Say Cheese!
Cheese!
I love this.
The little girls go and get the cheese
from the little boys?
That's adorable!
Aw, look at that poor little guy.
With his little boots.
Nobody picked him.
Oh, Marco.
Why don't you go up there?
No way.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
No.
Go take a bite of his cheese, young lady,
right now.
What?
I'm being tougher.
You know, like you said.
No, I meant be tougher on them.
Not me.
Oh, come on.
Just do it.
What's the worst that could happen?
Fine.
Hey there.
I'm Margo.
Hello, Margo.
I am Nico.
Would you like some of my cheese?
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you, Margo.
Thank you.
Hey, I am a great mother.
Do you see that, girls?
I laid down the...
Where are they?
Oh, Agnes.
Edith.
Hello.
Look!
A unicorn horn!
My little brain is going to explode!
Agnes, that's fake.
Oh, it's real, all right.
That horn came from the crooked forest.
The only place on earth where unicorns
still live.
Laugh, laugh, all of you!
They all think I'm crazy.
But I'm telling you, I saw one once with
my own eye.
Whoa, wait.
You saw a for real-life unicorn?
What did it look like?
Did you pet it?
Did it smell like candy?
What?
It was so fluffy.
I thought I was going to die.
Do you think maybe I could find one too?
Oh, they say if a maiden
pure of heart goes into the
crooked forest, the unicorn
will come and be hers forever.
Agnes!
Are you okay?
Yeah, we're fine.
Are you?
Unicorns are really real!
And I'm going to find one!
Sorry, went a little mama bear on you.
You know, I heard a scream
and... Yeah, okay, have a good one.
Wait for me here.
Don't!
Stop that!
You'll kick me!
Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Did you just steal candies?
Yes!
That's a lot of effort for two lollipops.
Snocky!
Oh, no!
The police!
What do we do?
Come on!
This is going to be fun!
The police are going to get us!
Bring it out!
Pigs!
Cops!
Take him with us!
Whoa!
They're back!
Yeah!
Man, that was crazy!
We're so close to getting busted!
Tell me about it.
I thought you were going to pee your
pants!
I did!
You did!
Mel, poof!
Hey, Mel!
The mastic!
The papaya!
Not the potato!
Hey, the potato!
The pizza!
Not to eat!
We're going to eat it all!
Come on!
Tempura!
Carbonara!
Hey, hey, hey!
Papama Luka!
Pippa!
Roo!
Get him!
Go, go!
Pippa!
Hands in the air!
Face it, Gru, villainy is in your blood!
You can't tell me you don't miss the rush
a little.
Maybe a little.
And now you got the chance to get back on
top, get your mojo back, become Gru again.
How awesome would that be?
Oh, please, come on.
Just one heist.
There's got to be something out there
somewhere that you still want to steal.
There is something.
How about we steal the largest diamond in
the world?
Yes!
I love it!
Thank you, brother.
Thank you from the bottom of my heart.
You know what?
We should do something to celebrate.
I've got the perfect idea.
Fritz, my good fellow, could you get me
another napkin, please?
I guess, of course, Miss Eden.
Hey, we're a Gru and Drew.
Here we are!
How's it going?
It's me, Gru.
And me, Drew.
I hug everybody whether they like it or
not.
Why are they pretending to be each other?
Oh, that's for dinner, but probably won't
like it.
I'm so grumpy all the time.
Hey, I laugh a lot, and I'm kind of an
idiot.
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
I'm busted in the gut.
Look at them!
They are total barns.
Oh, look, it's me, Gru.
And I'm Drew.
We switched places.
Oh, it's so nice to see you two are
getting along.
We are getting along perfectly.
Wait, did we just finish each other's
sentences?
Oh, that's delightful.
Not creepy at all.
And you're going to stop now though,
right?
Sorry, it's a twin thing.
Uh-huh.
So, what did you guys do today?
Nothing.
Okay, what does it say?
All done.
Pardon me.
Good night, everybody.
Hey, hey, hey, put the brakes on.
What's the rush?
I need to get to bed so I can wake up and
find a unicorn.
Good night.
What was that about?
Agnes thinks she's going to find a real
unicorn in the woods tomorrow.
She's totally freaking out.
I feel like someone's got to tell her the
truth.
Not it.
Oh, don't worry, parenting 101.
I get this.
And please bless that when I find a
unicorn, he'll want to come home with me.
And sleep in my room so that I can ride
him to school every day.
And he'll use his magical powers to help
me do math.
Amen.
Hey, Xo.
Big day tomorrow.
Yeah, I'm finally going to get to see a
unicorn for reals.
If I do, can I bring it home?
Please.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Tell you what, every unicorn you find,
you can bring it home.
I better build a big pet, right?
But, you know... There's a
chance that you might not find one.
Huh?
It might not be good unicorn finding
weather.
Um, they're tricky to find them.
And, I don't know, maybe...
Maybe...
Unicorns don't really...
...explore that part of the woods.
But the man said a maiden could find one
if she was pure in heart.
I'm pure in heart, right?
The purest.
Can we stop talking now?
I need to get to sleep.
Good night, sweetie.
Good night, girl.
I'm okay!
Hold on to me...
You can't really see... Hey!
Get that back!
You can't really see...
You can't really see!
We've been waiting a long time.
Can we... No, no, no!
Because I'm training for the big day.
Nobody's gonna stop me.
Because I am super-sassy, super-sassy,
super-sassy.
What's today's plan, boss?
What's the plan?
Silly robot, I'll show you the plan.
Time to watch a very special episode of
Evil Brat.
To see exactly what I'm gonna do to stupid
Tensel Town.
This week on Evil Brat!
It's a giant Evil Brat robot!
Open fire!
Nice try, coppers.
Chew on this!
He's shooting his super-sticky,
self-inflating gum!
Run!
Gum won, gum all!
Gum won, gum all.
Seriously, how did this show never win an
Emmy?
And now, it's your turn to shine,
my diamond!
Hey, Clive, I guess you could say our plan
was out of this world.
Now that's entertainment!
Come on, let's make it a reality.
Here we are, in the dark and creepy
crooked forest.
In search of the mythical unicorn.
For some reason.
And here she is, the fearless unicorn
hunter.
It can eat us, stop it!
You're gonna scare away the unicorn.
If somehow we actually find a unicorn,
I'm gonna film it and get rich.
Look over there!
This is it, this is where we're gonna see
it.
Unicorns, here we come!
What's that for?
Bait!
Duh.
Come on!
Now all we have to do is wait.
Okay, this is Brad's lair.
It may not look like much,
but this place is armed
with some of the most high-tech
weaponry known to man.
It's considered impenetrable.
But a piece of cake for us, right,
brother?
Yes, this is not like stealing lollipops.
Whoa!
This security system can detect an air
assault from any direction.
So we'll have to approach low and close to
the water.
Next.
Then there are these deadly spikes.
Covered with enough poison to blow your
mind.
Literally.
Good to know.
So here's the plan.
You're the getaway driver.
So you'll wait in the boat.
Wait, hold on.
Wait in the boat?
But I want to be in on the actions.
Through the getaway driver is the most
crucial part of any plan.
Do you know how hard it is?
Doing nothing, touching
nothing, with all of
the adrenaline coursing
through your veins.
And you must wait.
Can I count on you?
No.
I guess so.
So I'll climb up to the cube and enter
here.
And once I'm inside, find the diamond.
I've underestimated Brad before.
It's not going to be easy.
I think we can handle it.
That's villain suits!
This will make us unstoppable!
Whoa!
Achoo-wah-wah!
I call the black one!
It's call time!
Hello.
Oh, hi.
Hello, Mother Margo.
I am Nico.
I present you a pig to confirm my
engagement to your daughter.
Hey, what now?
What's going on?
Remember Little Boots?
Hello, my schmoopsy-poo.
Whoa, hey.
You seem to think you're engaged.
What?
We're not engaged.
Look, Nico, you seem like a very nice boy.
With a very nice pig.
But you're not engaged.
Okay?
It's not happening.
I understand.
Who was I kidding?
A dumpling like me with a goddess like
you.
But I promise, I will never forget you,
Margo.
Never.
Oh, I'm pretty sure I won't forget you
either.
Bye.
Bye, Nico.
Wow, that was crazy.
Whoa, that was totally humiliating.
Taking a bite of that cheese was the
stupidest thing I've ever done.
Why did I listen to you?
Right, but it's over now, so...
Here we go.
Nico.
You refuse my son's engagement,
pig?
What?
May you and your daughter
die a slow death and.
..
All right, lady, that's it.
Nobody, nobody curses my daughter.
You got that?
Because if you mess with Margo,
you mess with me.
And I promise you do not want to mess with
me.
Do you understand me?
Yes, yes.
Good.
Now, get!
Look, Margo, I think we just need to...
I have to tell Gru.
Can we go back now?
Already?
Just a couple more hours.
We have to be home before it gets dark.
I don't understand.
I did exactly what the man said.
You mean that one-eyed, scar-faced man
that everybody laughed at?
Yeah, it makes no sense.
Look, Agnes, maybe we're not...
My whole life has been building through
this moment!
It's a... Unicorn!
I can't believe it!
I'm gonna name you Lucky!
Oh, Lucky, stop it!
Yeah, I'll let someone else burst her
bubble.
Look at us, two brothers pulling the
heist!
And that diamond will make us the richest,
most powerful villains in the world!
Right, brother?
Bravo!
Bravo, Simo!
You're amazing!
I'm so sorry I'm so
embarrassed, I was very
rude, and you were
always such a gentleman!
You did it!
You got our jobs back!
Oh yeah, right, sure!
Oh look, we're here!
I'm going in!
Take the wheel!
I still don't see why I can't go with you!
Hey, hey, we discussed this, now is not
the time to mess with the plant!
Fine.
I
told you, you're supposed to stay with the
boat!
Oh, I didn't think you meant that
literally.
What other way could I have meant it?
Alright, let's move.
Just follow my lead.
Got it!
Help me!
Ow, ow, ow!
Oh no!
Where's the bikes?
They're gonna be bailed!
I'm okay!
I miss the minions.
Come on!
Coming!
It's a scaling device!
Quick, camouflage mold!
Freeze!
And close your eyes!
And cover your mouth!
Okay, take my hand!
Follow me!
My head!
I should have stayed in the boat!
My stomach feels all queasy!
I shouldn't have eaten that pot pie!
Come on, this way!
Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
I'm gonna get you!
You gotta leave your house.
Go inside out.
I know you're proud as A&G.
I know you're
so well you know what they say.
About this show, but even if you don't
play, It must go on.
You decided to stay.
You wanna be...
Do it, do it, do it!
One more time, tell me just guys to do it!
Looks like it's right above us!
Okay, what do I do?
Should I wait in the vent?
Now come with me.
Yes, I'd like to thank the economy.
I can help.
No, no, no, no, no!
I can do this!
Yes, yes, Paulie Ringwald, I will take you
to the boat.
Good, good!
Who's there?
Ninety-nine old Brad Balloons...
Oops, almost forgot!
Shhh, over here!
Stay close!
What?
Dolls!
Looks like Brad was the only one stupid
enough to buy this junk.
Oh, I used to have one of these!
Alright,
we're getting close.
From now on, every move must be made with
total precision and purpose.
Focus!
We're after the diamond, not the
bubblegum!
Got it!
Yum!
This way!
And now to put this where it belongs.
What?
Look at it, Clive.
It's beautiful!
Will you please shut up?
He's gonna spot us!
Intruders!
Freeze, dipsticks!
Gru, there's two of you now?
Then this will be twice as much fun!
Give me back my diamond!
Total lockdown!
We'll see!
Thank you for saving us!
Look, we got the diamond!
And we're going to... Take it to
the AVL and get our jobs back!
Wait!
What?
That's amazing!
And the best part is, you'll never ever go
behind my back ever again.
Right, honey bear?
Yeah, right.
Lesson learned.
The girls will start packing and tell them
the good news.
We're getting our jobs back!
Yes, yes, go tell the girls!
No, no way!
We can't give the diamond back!
I have to!
No, you don't!
Yes, I do!
Give it!
No, give it!
Ow!
What is wrong with you?
You kicked me!
You lied to me!
Hey, I would have told you the truth,
but you're too much of a wimp to handle it!
That's it, I'm out of here.
You have no right to take that!
We stole it together!
Together?
You gotta be kidding me!
You did nothing but screw up the whole
time!
I got this in spite of you!
Oh yeah?
Well, at least I didn't get fired from my
job like a total loser!
At least I had the job!
What have you accomplished that was so
great?
I'll tell you what!
Nothing!
No wonder Dad thought you were such a
failure.
We are no longer brothers!
That's fine with me!
Ow!
Honey, that's not actually a unicorn.
Huh?
But he has one horn.
I'm sorry, sweetie, but he's just a goat.
Life is just like that sometimes.
We're hoping for a unicorn, and we get a
goat.
Well, you know what?
Lucky is the best goat in the whole wide
world!
Look at that face!
I just want to squeeze it!
I'll take this.
You've been a bad boy, Gru.
Can you get the rest of the suitcases?
Come on, girls, let's go!
Let's get physical!
Change of plans, girls.
Instead of going home...
Eyebrows!
Ow!
We're going to Hollywood!
Now that's what I call acting!
Let's go, Clive!
We've got a giant robot waiting!
Lucy?
Brad!
He took the girls!
What?
No!
Drew!
Go away!
Brad has the girls!
Listen, brother, what about what I said?
No, I'm the one, but I
shouldn't have... I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Gru.
Look out!
What is that?
No, the plan!
Gru?
The plan has failed!
Gru!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
No, you can't leave me here!
I'm famous!
Clive, arm the cannons.
Cue arm this!
Don't!
Oh, don't worry, girls.
I've prepared a front row seat for you.
Once again,
I win and Gru loses!
Enjoy the show, girls!
What in the heck?
I hope the girls are okay!
Brad!
Brad and Clive!
He's on the left!
No!
I've seen this episode!
He's going to bubblegum the whole city and
send it up into space!
Hurry!
No!
This is it!
Lights!
Camera!
Laser!
The girls, you two go take care of Brad.
Wait, what are you doing?
Look at that laser go.
I love it when a plan comes together.
It's Gru!
Get ready, Brad!
You're about to be blasted back to the
80s!
There's more where that came from!
It'll take more than that to stop me.
Brad Pack, go get that barf bag.
Bonus!
Did you see that, Clive?
All gone!
Bye-bye, Wonder Twins.
Look at what we have here!
Sorry, Gru.
This is going to
be a total... Oh, no!
No, no, no, no,
no!
I've been a bad boy!
Nobody messes with my Gru!
What?
What's happening?
Hold on!
I'm coming!
You've ruined everything!
And now it's time to die.
Any last words, Gru?
You know what?
I got two words for you.
Dance fight.
Oh, it is unlike Donkey Kong.
I'm going to enjoy this!
My turn!
Game over!
Is this what you're looking for?
No!
Go!
Curse you, Gru!
Hey, we did it!
Yes, we did, brother.
Hey, Mal!
Welcome back!
I found what you and I
fought for you to remember we did this
together Love you, Mom.
Hi, Mama.
Tolga!
Boys, time for bed!
We're back at work in the morning.
I'm coming, sweetie!
Hi, Lucy!
See you tomorrow, brother.
Hey, I'm back on the job.
So no villainy tonight.
Got it?
I make no promises.
Love you!
Uh-huh, right.
I love you, too.
Alright, go to bed.
Hey, guys!
Come on!
What is happening?
It's coming from outside!
Hey!
I thought we said no more villainy!
Sorry, brother!
Somebody's got to keep the family
tradition alive!
Right?
Yeah!
Let's get him!
Honey, he's my brother!
You'll give him a five-minute head start.
Then the blue light use
Continues The front is in its tower
Singing the flag-burning blues Feel the
screws We don't care about no fence We
don't care about no trouble
The watchbook's taking it slow Now
everybody knows Here we go!
If you do You can throw the world out Look
at you
High and proud Oh,
just let the sun dry We
don't care about no fence We don't,
we just want to get in Let's make out like
we're lovers The watchbook's taking it
slow Now everybody knows Here we go!
Congratulations!
If you do
High and proud The watchbook's taking it
slow Now
everything you can kill Is the fun
Look at you High and proud Like a yellow
light
The watchbook's taking it slow Now
everybody
knows The watchbook's taking it slow Now
everybody knows Congratulations!
If you do You can throw the world out Look
at you I said, hey High and proud